For the love of - Josuke, are
you still playing that game?
If you don't turn it off right
this second, I'm gonna scream!
Five more minutes, please!
Just five more minutes!
Come on, Mom, just this once!
I can't stop now!
I'm about to get to the best part!
Quitting guarantees I'll
live the pathetic life of
a scrub who doesn't follow
through on his promise!
Have it your way!
The longer you play your little game, the
harder these kicks are gonna get! I don't!
How long do you think you can hold out?!
It's over. Shit.
Put it away and start your homework.
Oh, and would it kill you
to take off your uniform?
It is nighttime, you know.
Sorry, I can't see you anymore. Huh?
But why, Sachiko?
Have the flames of our love burned down?
What's going on?
I'm pretty sure that I turned it off.
Ah, come on, shut off, will ya?
It would seem Jotaro Kujo
has refused to leave town.
And after I went out of my way
to give him an explicit warning!
There has to be a reason, right?
Josuke Higashikata I know you!
You're Chili Pepper?
What are you doing here?
You're not the brightest bulb, are you?
Clearly it escaped your
notice that I've been
popping in and out of
here for a while now.
What?
This asshole's been keeping
tabs on me the entire time?
One of my other hot spots is
the house belonging to Okuyasu,
the brother of that fool I knocked off.
I'm also well aware of that schoolgirl
Yukako Yamagishi and Koichi Hiroze's reverb.
And I know Toshikazu Hazamada and
Tamami Kobayashi are in the hospital.
Something about this isn't making sense.
From everything I've seen, you're
a conniving, bird-brained coward.
What reason could you possibly
have for turning up at my house,
ready to take me on fair and square?
Surely you're not moronic
enough to believe that anything
you could do would actually
be enough to mess me up.
Me? Mess you up?
No, nothing so foul for this birdie.
Your death will be a humane one.
Huh, so you're a coward and a
comedian with a crappy sense of humor.
You're two for two, birdbrain.
Full disclosure before we begin,
I've already told Jotaro his Star
Platinum poses a great threat to me.
His vigilance is annoyingly steadfast,
and his stand's time-stopping
ability is formidable. So,
the only course of action left
to me is to completely decimate
that interloper in a head-to-head
battle for supremacy.
But before I fight, Jotaro,
I want to test my abilities
against you, Josuke Higashikata.
Why don't you come a little bit closer?
I won't fight!
All I'm asking you to
do is unleash an attack
as swift and precise as
one of star platinums.
It's as simple as that!
And if you're all the way back there,
I'm worried your punches
won't be quite up to snuff.
Is that mockery I'm
detecting in your voice?
No, not in the slightest.
I just have every confidence in the
capabilities of you and your stand,
so why don't you come closer?
I want you to give me your best
shot, so put your back into it, boy.
Here, come on.
Lay one on me.
Make sure to get nice and close.
Incredible!
So fast! I'll in the...
I'm tired of your incessant squawking!
He's faster than I ever imagined!
If you keep it up, I'll just
have to de-beak you myself!
And by the way, Jotaro's Star
Platinum's got nothing on me.
Don't ever forget that. Damn it!
My arrogance got the best of me,
and I underestimated his abilities!
What?
Josuke, what the hell is
going on in there? That blow,
it was like being on the receiving end
of a supercharged jet engine blast.
He might actually be stronger than Mr.
Jotaro.
Very impressive, Josuke.
I wasn't expecting your shining
diamond to be so robust.
It would appear that I'm not the
only one of us who's matured.
Clearly my time hasn't yet arrived.
Until Chili Pepper is stronger, vanquishing
Jotaro shall remain a far-off fantasy.
All he needs is a source of electricity
to pop out and pulverize us.
What's worse is he can
control his stand from afar.
Josuke, why did it sound like
50 tornadoes flew through here?
Don't know.
Maybe you're hearing things.
Ugh, damn it.
I just got bit by another bug.
You know, it's days like today.
I wish I was one of
those fancy bug zappers.
It's Josuke! Hey, guys.
I'm sorry for the wait.
What the heck is this all about, Josuke?
I mean, why'd you want to meet us all
the way out here in the boondocks?
Wouldn't Tony-O's or that cafe have been
a much better place to sit down and talk?
I wasn't the one who
called you guys out here.
It was actually Jotaro. Mr. Jotaro?
Wonder what he wants?
I'm guessing it's about chili pepper.
What?
When you say chili pepper, you don't mean
that horrible Stan Chili Pepper, do you?
So he's finally back.
Yeah.
In fact, he paid me a
visit at home last night.
You prick!
Why didn't you tell me
as soon as it happened?
Okuyasu.
He turns into a completely
different person anytime
he hears even the slightest
mention of chili pepper.
But how can you blame him when he
lost his brother to that stand?
I told Josuke not to say anything.
Discussing this downtown wasn't an option.
We'd be surrounded by electricity.
Mr. Jotaro!
I didn't want to risk being
spied on, so I had us meet here.
Okuyasu, just so you know, Chili Pepper
grates the ever-loving shit out of me, too.
That slithery bastard thinks he can
do whatever he damn well pleases.
He spies on people, eavesdrops,
swipes anything he wants.
Wait a minute,
so that's why I woke up to my homework
being gone from my desk the other day?
It makes total sense to me now!
And here I thought my mom threw it
away when she took out the trash!
Do you really think now's the
time to worry about that, Koichi?
Look, this is the bottom line.
The only reason Chili Pepper hasn't raised
even more hell is because we're around.
But don't let that fool you, he's
a lot stronger than he lets on.
He can drag anyone he wants into the phone
lines as easy as making a prank call.
There's no doubt he has the bow and arrow.
Right now, we need to focus
on who he's shot with it.
I know firsthand how much
stronger he's gotten.
We have to find Chili Pepper's
user as soon as humanly possible.
But how do we do that?
Well, we're here to
figure it out together.
Right, Mr. Jotaro?
No, not really.
But we found someone to do just that.
And the three of you will
be pleased to know our guest
of honor is arriving at the
Port of Morioh at noon today.
Just who is this someone?
Hold on, is he a stand user?
He is.
The name of his stand is Hermit Purple,
but he's gotten way too old to
risk going out into the field.
Fighting as a whole is
out of the question.
What?
Just how old is this guy?
I mean, you have met
him before, haven't you?
Yeah, I know him quite well, actually.
He used to be pretty
studly back in the day.
But you wouldn't know it looking at him
now he's 80 no make that 79 years old.
79 the guy's practically a
fossil his legs definitely
aren't what they used
to be so he uses a cane
and two years ago he had
gallstones removed not
to mention his cataracts
all his teeth are fake now
so he grumbles about
missing his t-bone stakes
oh and he's going senile
to give it a rest next
you're gonna tell me he
likes to talk to mailboxes
come on you have gotta be
yanking our chains the real
reason i had you guys
come here was so that you
could protect the old man
if chili pepper gets wind
of his arrival you can
bet he'll stop at nothing
to take him down the thing
he dreads most is one of
us discovering the true
identity of his user but
that doesn't explain how
the old timer is gonna help
us i was against it too
but as soon as he heard
about the bow and arrow he
headed to japan despite.
to Japan?
So this person isn't
Japanese, Mr. Jotaro? Correct.
Josuke, this is life-changing! Huh? What
is? What do you mean? Think about it!
He's a 79-year-old Stan
user who isn't from Japan!
Hey, you can't mean...
That's what I needed to hear!
Watch out! It's Chili Pepper!
Blast it!
How'd he find his way out here?
But how?
There aren't any power lines in this area!
He used a motorcycle battery.
He must have hidden inside it
and come here with Okuyasu.
He hijacked my bike!
And he heard everything!
So, the port of Mariah at noon.
That's where I'll find the old fogey
of a stand user who can locate me, huh?
The moment that Caesar pulls into port,
I'll rip him up and continue
my reign of debauchery!
Dammit, he knows about the old man.
In other words, he knows
about Josuke's father.
At the speed he's going,
actually Pepper will get to the old
man before we can get him to safety.
Quick, Josuke!
Use your stand to chuck a rock or
something at that bike and take it down!
Don't even think about it!
That piece of shit is mine!
I'm gonna crush that murdering jailbird
into dust if it's the last thing I do!
He cut through space itself!
Damn!
It's Keijo's little brother!
What's the rush?
We have unfinished business!
It's time for you to disappear!
Well done, boy! Well done!
Teleporting yourself to the motorcycle
was exceptional, to say the least!
But you wasted your time!
That adorable scratching
motion you do with a hand is
hardly a match for Chili
Pepper's extraordinary speed,
so as usual,
I'm afraid your efforts
have been all for naught!
Face backs, kid!
You're slow!
Take another look, dickhead!
When I said I'd make something
disappear, I'm at the motorcycle!
He destroyed the front wheel!
It's safe to say you
won't be escaping now.
That's using your head,
Okuyasu. Way to go!
Luckily for us,
Chili Pepper won't be able to move very
far away from the motorcycle battery.
And check it out!
The nearest power line is
at least 100 meters away.
We've got you cornered
like a rat in a trap.
That was a close one.
Hey, stay focused, he isn't captured yet.
Don't forget he can still
use the bike's battery.
He'll do whatever it takes to
kill Okuyasu and fly the coop.
Let's head over.
Right.
Color me surprised.
I didn't think you'd go to all
this trouble to avenge Keicho.
I didn't.
I knew who my bro was.
The other shoe was gonna drop eventually.
Finally, someone was bound to
snuff him out over something.
That's the thing about crime.
No matter how far you try to run from it,
it always has a way of
catching up to you in the end.
That's painfully clear,
even to a sap like me.
So now for the business at hand.
Tell me who your user
is and where he lives.
Do that and I'll spare your life,
which is more than you deserve.
Interesting.
If I tell you, you'll spare me, huh?
You're surprisingly composed.
I was positive your bowels would be
burning with vengeful fury by now!
To be honest, I'm secretly hoping you
won't give me the info on your user.
I mentioned to scrape you away,
you glow-in-the-dark shithead.
So give me a reason.
There's the real you!
Thinking you can kill me?
With that sluggish right hand.
I don't know if I should laugh or yawn,
but either way you won't be
putting out my lights today.
You bastard!
I'll end you!
And I'll make sure you realize
how pathetic your stand
is when compared to the
marvel that is Chili Pepper!
Now do you finally understand how slow
you are? Okuyasu! Okuyasu! Not good.
Here comes Jotaro.
I can't stick around much longer.
Huh?
How'd he get behind me?
You're right about me being slow,
and I may have missed the mark,
but I swiped away space, which
gives me the ability to teleport.
Did you forget about that?
How do you like that?
You big-nosed freak!
I might be wrong, but it seems
like you're not as fast as before.
Do you think someone as slow as
you can slip by my next attack?
Look, you guys.
Chili Pepper's electric charge is fading.
He's getting weaker and
weaker by the second.
His stand must be running out of power.
Well, would you look at that.
He actually did it.
Okuyasu, leave him alive.
We'll handle him once we get over there.
You've already won.
Now our primary focus needs to be getting
him to tell us where
the bow and arrow are.
You're right about one thing.
My energy is fading.
Your stand may be as slow as molasses,
but the ferocity of his attack
is downright bone-chilling.
That being said, don't you want to finish
off your brother's killer for good?
Try using your head for a moment.
How can you be certain I'm not
simply pretending to be frail?
Okuyasu...
What?
Who's to say I'm not luring Jotaro in
close so I can cleave off his head?
Quit spouting bullshit!
Fine by me.
So what'll it be?
Will you do away with me now?
Or wait for me to get the drop on Jotaro?
You bastard.
Hold on a minute.
If you were really up to something
shady, why would you tell me your plan?
Had he just kept his beak shut, he
could have easily played us all.
He would have been in the perfect
position to take me and Jotaro out.
And if that's the case,
since he basically told me
nothing's wrong with him,
the chances of him attacking
me are practically zero.
At least I think they are.
Are you trying to say you
want me to kill you after all?
I'll let you come to your own conclusions.
This is so confusing!
Is he on his last legs?
Or is he lying through his
beak waiting to attack?
Which one is it?
What's your answer?
Are you gonna do it or not?
If this asshole isn't really injured,
I have to kill him right here and now.
But is that the right move?
He could have something up his sleeve.
Shit! Should I?
Okuyasu, I better get over there.
Last chance.
Make up your mind, Okuyasu.
The hell with it!
I'm putting an end to this
nightmare once and for all!
It's time to die!
Okuyasu!
Don't even think about
trying to stop me, Jotaro!
He killed my bro!
That means he has to
pay the ultimate price!
That's the only truth
that matters right now!
And my heart has shown
me what I need to do!
Now eat, shit, and die,
you glorified nightlight!
Well, that's just great.
Finding the bow and arrow is going
to be a real pain in the ass now.
At least he settled
things with that freak.
Hang on.
Something doesn't feel right.
We need to be careful.
My gut's telling me Chili
Pepper is still a threat.
Underground electrical cables?
That bastard!
He faked all that so I'd expose them!
Not quite.
I really was fading.
That motorcycle battery
only holds 12 volts.
A few moments longer and I
would have been done for!
I must thank you for reviving me!
Poor simple-minded Okuyasu.
If only you'd been a good boy and
controlled yourself as Totoro instructed,
I would have faded away with the battery.
I know the location of every electrical
line running through this town.
My original plan was to
escape into those cables,
but they were too far
away from the motorcycle.
And in the state I was in, digging
them up was out of the question.
Why won't you die?
He's faster than before.
With this much electricity at my disposal,
I have more than enough
power to challenge?
your lackluster right hand.
Ah!
Okuyasu!
I seem to remember your
brother Keicho saying
something about you never
failing to hold him back.
Oh, how right he was.
Your soul is underdeveloped.
Ah-ha-ha!
Revenge was never going to be within
your reach, you cocksure ignoramus!
So long, Jotaro and Josuke.
I'm taking off!
But not before I find that
old coot Joseph Joestar?
And see to it that he
shares the same fate!
as the lamentable Nijimura brothers!
To the victor go the spoils!
Okuyasu, no!
He pulled him into the cables!
Okuyasu! Okuyasu!
Good grief.
To think we were that close
and he still got away.
That stand was absolutely terrifying.
How do you even begin to fight
a remote stand with boundless
power to tap into every
electrical company within reach?
What the hell are you guys talking about?!
Okuyasu was...
He was murdered in cold blood and you're
rambling about how strong the enemy was?!
Oh yeah, you're right.
We should check up on Okuyasu.
Leave it to me.
There's one consolation in all this.
He must have had a guardian
angel looking out for him.
Weird as it sounds,
his right arm getting chopped off was
the best thing that could have happened.
Huh?
Let's go, Shining Diamond!
You don't have to worry,
so dry those tears, Koichi.
Once I fix his arm, his
body will come back.
What the hell?
All right!
I thought we lost you for good, Okuyasu!
Shit!
I... I...
I was totally outclassed by that bastard!
It's not about revenge, and
we can't focus on setbacks.
Joseph Joestar.
He's the priority here. He needs us.
I know it's tough,
but that's how we're gonna beat
Chili Pepper and get true justice.
You have to do this for our town.
And if that isn't enough, then do it
for all the people you care about.
I might be stating the
obvious, but this isn't good.
Guess I was taking this too lightly.
Yeah, we have to reach the old
man's boat before Chili Pepper.
Let's head to the port.
How can you be so nonchalant
at a time like this?
Look at Okuyasu, he's
still in shock over here.
We can get to the port
faster this way. Sounds good.
Would you guys wait for us?
There's no way around it, bro.
Mario, in order to beat Chili
Pepper, I have to surpass you.
Mr.
Joestar, we'll be arriving at
the Port of Mario any moment now.
In the face of the humic
and of all that I need
to I want to come stand
a little bit closer.
Breathe in and get a bit higher you'll
never know what hit you when I get to you.
Oh I want you I don't know if I
need you but oh I gotta find you.
Breakdown, breakdown.